# Ranim Khojah



linkedin.com/in/ranimkhojah



rankhojah@gmail.com

#### **Summary**

As a highly motivated Software Engineering and Management graduate with a great passion for AI and Natural Language Processing, I am aiming to continue along the AI path by earning a Master's degree in Language Technology (2020-2022), learn more from practice and gain new skills and experience in the AI industry. After I graduate, I will carry on improving myself and sharpening my skills to become an expert in the AI/ NLP field.

As a Master's student in Language Technology, I will apply what I learn in practice as well as to adapt to the job I'll be doing in the industry, starting from technologies to practices and processes followed.

Throughout my Bachelor's studies, I believe that I became a quick learner and acknowledged how important time-management to ensure effectiveness and efficiency when balancing multiple activities such as managing both studies and work.

I've done a few projects that involve AI, especially NLP, in academic and personal projects. A personality type predictor and an NLP-based tool to optimize test case prioritization are the ones that stand out. More projects can be found in my portfolio: ranimkhojah.github.io

#### **Experience**

# Teaching Assistant

University of Gothenburg Sep 2018 - Jun 2020 (1 year 10 months)

#### Co-Founder and Software developer

CTRL+ALT+TEAM
Sep 2017 - Apr 2019 (1 year 8 months)

#### **Education**

### University of Gothenburg

Bachelor's degree, Software Engieering and Management 2017 - 2020

## 🗎 Eksjövux - Eksjö

Svenska som Andra Språk (SAS) 2016 - 2017

#### Skills

Python (Programming Language) • JavaScript • Java • Agile Methodologies • spaCy • TensorFlow • Text Classification • R (Programming Language) • SQL • Git